<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Introducing Kosli on Kosli developer documentation</title><link>https://docs.kosli.com/introducing_kosli/</link><description>Recent content in Introducing Kosli on Kosli developer documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://docs.kosli.com/introducing_kosli/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Organizations</title><link>https://docs.kosli.com/introducing_kosli/organizations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.kosli.com/introducing_kosli/organizations/</guid><description>Organizations # Organization in Kosli owns Kosli pipelines and environments - which means only members of the organization can get access to them. By default, when you sign up to Kosli, a personal organization is created for you and the name of the organization matches your user name. Only you can access your personal organization.
You can also create shared organizations, and invite other Kosli users as members, so they can see and report to your Kosli pipelines and environments.</description></item><item><title>Environments</title><link>https://docs.kosli.com/introducing_kosli/environments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.kosli.com/introducing_kosli/environments/</guid><description>Environments # Environments in Kosli provide a place to track how your systems change over time.
Each runtime environment you'd like to track in Kosli should have its own Kosli environment created - e.g. if you use k8s cluster to host qa, staging and production versions of your product you create 3 separate environments for those in Kosli.
Kosli supports different type of runtime environments and the reporting command varies for each:</description></item><item><title>Pipelines</title><link>https://docs.kosli.com/introducing_kosli/pipelines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.kosli.com/introducing_kosli/pipelines/</guid><description>Pipelines # Pipelines in Kosli provide a place to report and track artifact status and related events from your CI pipelines.
Best practice is to create Kosli pipeline for each type of artifact - e.g. if your CI pipeline prpduces 3 separate artifacts (that could be 3 different binaries for three different platforms) you'd create 3 different Kosli pipelines to report artifacts and evidences.
You can create Kosli pipeline using our cli with kosli pipeline declare command.</description></item><item><title>Fingerprint</title><link>https://docs.kosli.com/introducing_kosli/fingerprint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.kosli.com/introducing_kosli/fingerprint/</guid><description>Fingerprint # Every time artifact is reported to Kosli a SHA256 digest of it is calculated. It doesn't matter if the artifact is a single file, a directory or a docker image - we can always calculate SHA256.
Fingerprints are used to connect the information recorded in Kosli - about environments, deployments and approval - to matching artifact.
You can also use Kosli CLI to calculated the fingerprint of any artifact locally.</description></item><item><title>CLI</title><link>https://docs.kosli.com/introducing_kosli/cli/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.kosli.com/introducing_kosli/cli/</guid><description>CLI # In order to record environments , artifacts and events to Kosli you need to use Kosli CLI . The same tool can be used to search Kosli and find out all you need to know about your runtime environments and artifacts.
Our CLI in an open source tool written in go and it's available for a number of different platforms.
To learn more about to install Kosli CLI click here Usage # Reference section contains all the information you may need to run Kosli CLI.</description></item><item><title>Web UI</title><link>https://docs.kosli.com/introducing_kosli/web_ui/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.kosli.com/introducing_kosli/web_ui/</guid><description>Web UI # app.kosli.com is an easy way to monitor the status of your environments and pipelines. All you need to log in is a GitHub account.
On the left of the page you can see the menu where you can:
Switch to another organization using dropdown menu Switch to the Environments or the Pipelines view Enter organization settings page Access this documentation page In the top right corner of the page you will see your GitHub avatar where you can access your profile settings (containing your Kosli api key).</description></item></channel></rss>