<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>How to on Kosli developer documentation</title><link>https://docs.kosli.com/how_to/</link><description>Recent content in How to on Kosli developer documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://docs.kosli.com/how_to/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Record</title><link>https://docs.kosli.com/how_to/record/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.kosli.com/how_to/record/</guid><description>Record your environments in Kosli # Recording the status of runtime environments it's one of the fundamental features of Kosli. Our CLI detects artifacts running in given environment and reports the information to Kosli.
If the list of running artifacts is different than what was reported previously a new snapshot is created. Snapshots are immutable and can't be tampered with.
There is range of kosli environment report [...] commands, allowing you to report a variety of environments.</description></item><item><title>Connect</title><link>https://docs.kosli.com/how_to/connect/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.kosli.com/how_to/connect/</guid><description>Connect your pipeline events # Kosli allows you to connect the development world (commits, builds, tests, approvals, deployments) with what’s happening in operations. There is a variety of commands that let you report all the necessary information to Kosli and - relying on automatically calculated fingerprints of your artifacts - match it with the environments.
Create a pipeline # In order to be able to report artifacts to Kosli you need to create a Kosli pipeline first.</description></item><item><title>Search</title><link>https://docs.kosli.com/how_to/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.kosli.com/how_to/search/</guid><description>Get your artifacts and environments information from Kosli # All the information stored in Kosli may be helpful both for operations and development. A set of get, ls, log and inspect commands allows you to quickly access the information about your environments, artifacts and deployments, without leaving your development environment.
Visit Reference to learn more about how to run each command.
The same CLI you use to record and connect your changes can be use to search for and browse information in Kosli.</description></item></channel></rss>