<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Kosli Overview on Kosli developer documentation</title><link>https://docs.kosli.com/kosli_overview/</link><description>Recent content in Kosli Overview on Kosli developer documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://docs.kosli.com/kosli_overview/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What is Kosli?</title><link>https://docs.kosli.com/kosli_overview/what_is_kosli/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.kosli.com/kosli_overview/what_is_kosli/</guid><description>What is Kosli? # Kosli records data from your CI pipelines and runtime environments, allowing you to query life after git from the command line.
Below you can read about what elements Kosli consists of.
Organization # An Organization in Kosli &amp;quot;owns&amp;quot; Kosli pipelines and environments - which means only members of each organization can get access to environments and pipelines that belong to the organization. By default, when you sign up to Kosli, a personal organization is created for you and the name of the organization matches your user name.</description></item><item><title>How to use Kosli?</title><link>https://docs.kosli.com/kosli_overview/kosli_tools/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.kosli.com/kosli_overview/kosli_tools/</guid><description>How to use Kosli? # CLI # In order to record environments, artifacts and evidence to Kosli you need to use the Kosli CLI. The CLI can be used to search Kosli and find out all you need to know about your runtime environments and artifacts.
Our CLI is an open source tool written in go and it's available for a number of different platforms.
Installing the Kosli CLI # Kosli CLI can be installed from package managers, by Curling pre-built binaries, or by running inside a Docker container.</description></item><item><title>Kosli integrations</title><link>https://docs.kosli.com/kosli_overview/kosli_integrations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.kosli.com/kosli_overview/kosli_integrations/</guid><description> Kosli integrations # CI/CD - run Kosli reporting commands easier with support for popular CI/CD tools Slack - receive slack notifications about changes in your environments status</description></item></channel></rss>